question_data = [{
    'category': 'Quiz',
    'type': 'multiple',
    'difficulty': 'medium',
    'question': 'Light curves can only be generated for\n some measure of brightness which is measured over time.',
    'correct_answer': 'False',
    'incorrect_answers': ['True', '', '']
},
    {
    'category': 'Quiz',
    'type': 'multiple',
    'difficulty': 'medium',
    'question': 'Light curves are:',
    'correct_answer': 'Graphs that show the brightness of an object over a period of time.',
    'incorrect_answers': ['Graphs that show the brightness of an object during its whole life.', 'Graphs that show the darkness of an object during its whole life.', 'Graphs that show the darkness of an object over a period of time.']
    },
    {'category': 'Quiz',
    'type': 'multiple',
    'difficulty': 'medium',
    'question': 'The changes in brightness that\n a light curve provides can help astronomers:',
    'correct_answer': 'Understand processes of the object they\n are studying and identify specific categories of stellar events',
    'incorrect_answers': ['Do experiments in a lab', 'Observe the universe and learn\n more things about extraterrestrial life', 'Predict their future']
     },
    {
        'category': 'Quiz',
        'type': 'multiple',
        'difficulty': 'medium',
        'question': 'Astronomers can identify cepheids not\n only in out Galaxy, but in other nearby galaxies as well',
        'correct_answer': 'True',
        'incorrect_answers': ['False', '', '']
    },
    {
        'category': 'Quiz',
        'type': 'multiple',
        'difficulty': 'medium',
        'question': 'Cataclysmic variables (CVs) are:',
        'correct_answer': 'Binary star systems that have\n a white dwarf and a normal star companion.',
        'incorrect_answers': ['Binary star systems that have\n a blue dwarf and a star companion.', 'Binary star systems that have\n a red dwarf and a normal star companion.', 'Binary star systems that have\n a white dwarf and a star companion.']
    },
    {
        'category': 'Quiz',
        'type': 'multiple',
        'difficulty': 'medium',
        'question': 'Check the correct answer:',
        'correct_answer': 'The white dwarf is often referred to as the\n "primary" star, and the normal star as the "companion" or the "secondary" star. ',
        'incorrect_answers': ['The white dwarf is often referred to as the "secondary" star,\n and the normal star as the "companion" or the "primary" star.', 'The white dwarf is often referred to as the "secondary" star,\n and the normal star as the "companion" or the "main" star.', 'The white dwarf is often referred to as the "primary" star,\n and the normal star as the "companion" or the "minor" star.']
    },
    {
        'category': 'Quiz',
        'type': 'multiple',
        'difficulty': 'medium',
        'question': 'Check the correct answer:',
        'correct_answer': 'There are probably more than a million of these cataclysmic\n variables in the galaxy, but only those near our Sun (several hundreds) have been studied in X-rays so far.',
        'incorrect_answers': ['There are probably less than a million of these cataclysmic variables in the galaxy,\n but only those near our Sun (several hundreds) have been studied in X-rays so far.', 'There are probably more than a billion of these cataclysmic variables in the galaxy,\n but only those near our Sun (several hundreds) have been studied in X-rays so far.', 'There are probably more than a million of these cataclysmic variables in the galaxy\n and all of them have been studied in X-rays so far.']
    },
    {
        'category': 'Quiz',
        'type': 'multiple',
        'difficulty': 'medium',
        'question': 'Dwarf novae outbursts are smaller in amplitude\n and higher in frequency than classical novae.',
        'correct_answer': 'True',
        'incorrect_answers': ['False',' ', '']
    },
    {
        'category': 'Quiz',
        'type': 'multiple',
        'difficulty': 'medium',
        'question': 'Cepheid Variables are:',
        'correct_answer': 'Stars which brighten and dim periodically.This behavior allows them to be used as\n cosmic yardsticks out to distances of a few tens of millions of light-years.',
        'incorrect_answers': ['Planets or stars which brighten and dim periodically. This behavior allows them to be used as\n cosmic yardsticks out to distances of a few tens of millions of light-years.','Stars which brighten and dim regularly. This behavior allows them to be used as\n cosmic yardsticks out to distances of a few tens of millions of light-years.', 'Stars which brighten and dim periodically. This behavior does not allow them to be used as\n cosmic yardsticks out to distances of a few tens of millions of light-years.']
    },
    {
        'category': 'Quiz',
        'type': 'multiple',
        'difficulty': 'medium',
        'question': 'Cepheids are very special variable stars because their period\n (the time they take to brighten, dim and brighten again) is:',
        'correct_answer': 'A uniform function of their brightness.',
        'incorrect_answers': ['Changes with time','Rarely', 'Does not relate with the brightness of the star']
    }

]
